const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '3×0＝', answer: '0', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '3×1＝', answer: '3', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '3×2＝', answer: '6', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '3×3＝', answer: '9', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '3×4＝', answer: '12', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '3×5＝', answer: '15', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '3×6＝', answer: '18', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '3×7＝', answer: '21', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '3×8＝', answer: '24', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '3×9＝', answer: '27', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 11, question: '3×10＝', answer: '30', image_name: '', etc_1: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];